export const SelectDifficulty = ["Any", "Easy", "Medium", "Hard"];

export const questions = [
  {
    question: "An algebraic expression containing three terms is called a",
    option1: "monomial",
    option2: "binomial",
    option3: "trinomial",
    option4: "all of these",
    correctOption: "3",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Easy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Number of terms in the expression $3x^{2}y - 2y^{2}z - z^{2}x + 5$ is",
    option1: "2",
    option2: "3",
    option3: "4",
    option4: "5",
    correctOption: "3",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Easy",
  },
  {
    question: "The terms of expression $4x^{2} - 3xy$ are:",
    option1: "$4x^{2}$ and $-3xy$",
    option2: "$4x^{2}$ and $3xy$",
    option3: "$4x^{2}$ and $-xy$",
    option4: "$x^{2}$ and $xy$",
    correctOption: "1",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Easy",
  },
  {
    question: "Factors of $-5x^{2}y^{2}z$ are",
    option1: "$-5.x.y.z$",
    option2: "$-5.x^{2}.y.z$",
    option3: "$-5.x.x.y.y.z$",
    option4: "$-5.x.y.z^{2}$",
    correctOption: "3",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Medium",
  },
  {
    question: "Coefficient of x in $-9xy^{2}z$ is",
    option1: "$9y.z$",
    option2: "$-9y.z$",
    option3: "$9y^{2}.z$",
    option4: "$-9y^{2}.z$",
    correctOption: "4",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Medium",
  },
  {
    question: "The subtraction of 5 times of y from x is",
    option1: "$5x - y$",
    option2: "$y - 5x$",
    option3: "$x - 5y$",
    option4: "$5y - x$",
    correctOption: "3",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Easy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The side length of the top of a square table is x. The expression for perimeter is:",
    option1: "$4 + x$",
    option2: "$2x$",
    option3: "$4x$",
    option4: "$8x$",
    correctOption: "3",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Medium",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The expression for the number of diagonals that we can make from one vertex of a n sided polygon is:",
    option1: "$2n + 1$",
    option2: "$n - 2$",
    option3: "$5n + 2$",
    option4: "$n - 3$",
    correctOption: "4",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Hard",
  },
  {
    question: "$123x^{2}y - 138x^{2}y$ is a like term of",
    option1: "$10xy$",
    option2: "$-15xy$",
    option3: "$-15xy^{2}$",
    option4: "$10x^{2}y$",
    correctOption: "4",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Hard",
  },
  {
    question: "The value of $3x^{2} - 5x + 3$ when $x = 1$ is",
    option1: "1",
    option2: "0",
    option3: "-1",
    option4: "11",
    correctOption: "1",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Easy",
  },
  {
    question: "$(2^{20} \\div 2^{15}) \\times 2^{3} =$",
    option1: "$2^{15}$",
    option2: "$2^{8}$",
    option3: "$2^{5}$",
    option4: "None of these",
    correctOption: "2",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Hard",
  },
  {
    question: "$(5/6)^{0} =$",
    option1: "1",
    option2: "6/5",
    option3: "0",
    option4: "None of these",
    correctOption: "1",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Easy",
  },
  {
    question: "If $(2^{2})^{n} = (2^{3})^{4}$, then n =",
    option1: "4",
    option2: "3",
    option3: "12",
    option4: "6",
    correctOption: "4",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Medium",
  },
  {
    question: "$(-7/5)^{-1} =$",
    option1: "5/7",
    option2: "-5/7",
    option3: "7/5",
    option4: "None of these",
    correctOption: "2",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Medium",
  },
  {
    question: "$81^{5} \\div (3^{2})^{5} =$",
    option1: "$3^{10}$",
    option2: "$3^{2}$",
    option3: "$3^{5}$",
    option4: "None of these",
    correctOption: "1",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Medium",
  },
  {
    question: "$(8^{2} \\times 8^{4}) - 2^{18} =$",
    option1: "$2^{2}$",
    option2: "$2^{4}$",
    option3: "0",
    option4: "None of these",
    correctOption: "3",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Hard",
  },
  {
    question: "$(3^{7}) \\div (81 \\times 3^{3}) =$",
    option1: "3",
    option2: "$3^{2}$",
    option3: "$3^{0}$",
    option4: "None of these",
    correctOption: "3",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Hard",
  },
  {
    question: "$(1/4)^{-3} - (1/3)^{-3} =$",
    option1: "37",
    option2: "1/37",
    option3: "-37",
    option4: "-1/37",
    correctOption: "1",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Medium",
  },
  {
    question:
      "$(10 \\times 5^{n+1} + 25 \\times 5^{n}) \\div (3 \\times 5^{n+2} + 10 \\times 5^{n+1})$",
    option1: "3/5",
    option2: "1",
    option3: "0",
    option4: "5",
    correctOption: "1",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Hard",
  },
  {
    question:
      "$(-1)^{50} \\times (-1)^{51} \\times (1)^{100} \\times (-1)^{101} =$",
    option1: "-1",
    option2: "1",
    option3: "0",
    option4: "2",
    correctOption: "2",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Easy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Find the mode for the data set, which shows the heights(in inches) of 10 students in a class: 60, 65, 63, 62, 65, 70, 62, 68, 60, 65",
    option1: "62",
    option2: "65",
    option3: "70",
    option4: "60",
    correctOption: "2",
    marksAllocated: 1,
    difficultyLevel: "Hard",
  },
];
